Guide to the Sussex Correspondence
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, Series I
  - "S"
    - Stewart, John, fl. 1820-1850
      - 3 ALS to the Duke of Sussex, Swaffham, 1826-31 (Box 2, Folder 137)
        Sends verses. Commended by Dr. Parr. With list of subscribers to his Bible Gems, 2nd series.
    - Stiles, J., Admiral. ALS to the Duke of Sussex, London, [1828 or later] (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - "T"
    - Tod, James, 1782-1835. ALS to T. J. Pettigrew, Croydon, 1829 Jun 5 (Box 2, Folder 139)
      Koran presented to the Duke of Sussex.
  - "V"
    - Vaughn, Robert, 1795-1868. ALS to the Duke of Sussex, Holland Park Terrace, 1830 Jan 25 (Box 2, Folder 140)
      Life of Wycliffe.
    - Victor, M. ALS to the Duke of Sussex, London, n.y. Jun 15 (Box 2, Folder 141)
      Concerning patronage of a series of "lectures dramatiques."
    - Vulliamy, Benjamin Lewis, 1780-1854
      - 2 ALS to T. J. Pettigrew, Pall Mall, 1828, 1830 (Box 2, Folder 142)
        A letter for the Duke of Sussex and his papers on Public Clocks.
      - 2 ALS to the Duke of Sussex, Pall Mall, 1828, 1830 (Box 2, Folder 143)
        Presents his paper on Public Clocks and a Supplement.
  - "W"
    - Wade, Arthur S., 1789-1845. ALS to the Duke of Sussex, Tavistock St., 1829 Jun 11 (Box 2, Folder 144)
    - Walker, John Forsyte, ca. 1783-1848. AL to the Duke of Sussex, Blackheath, 1828 Jan 2 (Box 2, Folder 145)
      Sends prospectus of his book.
    - Walker, Patrick
      - ALS to T. J. Pettigrew, Edinburgh, 1830 Nov 10 (Box 2, Folder 146)
        Introducing Patrick Walker, engraver.
      - ALS to the Duke of Sussex, 36 GT Marlborough St., 1830 Aug 10 (Box 2, Folder 147)
        Elected to the Maitland Club.
    - Walter, W. A.
      - AL to T. J. Pettigrew, British Museum, [1827?] (Box 2, Folder 148)
        Will wait on the Duke of Sussex as directed.
      - ALS to the Duke of Sussex, British Museum, 1827 Mar 28 (Box 2, Folder 149)
        Translation of Niebuhr's Roman History.
    - Walthers, R. ALS to the Duke of Sussex, Sloane Street, 1824 Jan 16 (Box 2, Folder 150)
      Concerning his steam-powered artificial incubator for poultry.
    - Wilks, John, 1765?-1854. ALS to the Duke of Sussex, Finsbury Square, 1822 Mar 22 (Box 2, Folder 151)
      Anniversary, Institution for Education of the Poor.
    - Wilson, John, 1774-1865. ALS to the Duke of Sussex, [n.p.], n.d. (Box 2, Folder 152)
      Shortly after the appointment of Sir James Graham.
    - Wilson, William Rae, 1772-1849. ALS to the Duke of Sussex, Berlin, 1817 Aug 14 (Box 2, Folder 153)
      Account of his recent travels.
    - Wirgman, Thomas. ALS to the Duke of Sussex, Crawley, 1824 May 29 (Box 2, Folder 154)
      Presents a copy of Transcendental Philosophy.
    - Withers, W[illiam?]. ALS to the Duke of Sussex, Holt, 1828 Jan 12 (Box 2, Folder 155)
      Presents a copy of his letter on the planting of fruit trees.
    - Wood, William, 1774-1857. ALS to the Duke of Sussex, 20 Great George Street, 1831 Jun 25 (Box 2, Folder 156)
      Seeks to sell William Phillips's "works on Minerals, with the Catalogue" on behalf of his widow.
    - Wright, Waller Rodwell, d. 1826. ALS to the Duke of Sussex, 54 Hams Place, 1814 Jan 25 (Box 2, Folder 157)
      Drawing of a Knight Templar.
    - Wylie, John. ALS to the Duke of Sussex, Glasgow, 1831 Feb 16 (Box 2, Folder 158)
      Presents a set of the Maitland Club publications.
  - "Y"
    - Young, Mary. ALS to the Duke of Sussex, Regents Park, 1830 Jul 28 (Box 2, Folder 159)
      Encloses prospectus of proposed book.
  - "Z"
    - Zuccarelli, P. ALS to [T. J. Pettigrew], 110 Gt Portland St., 1827 Jul 12 (Box 2, Folder 160)
      A sitting by the Duke of Sussex for his bust.
    - Zunz, Leopold, 1794-1886. ALS in German to the Duke of Sussex, Berlin, 1830 Sep 11 (Box 2, Folder 161)
      Sends two small manuscripts. Accompanied by contemporary English translation.
  - Unidentified
    - Unidentified ALS to the Duke of Sussex., n.d. (Box 2, Folder 162)